Hassan Jafari

Mobile: 0450302353 |

E-mail: hassanjafari803@gmail.com

PERSONAL SUMMARY

Accounting Bookkeeper, Accounting Assistant, Accounting Clerk, Administration Officer and Finance

Manager with over 22 years of related experience in the Finance, Accounting, and Office fields. In May

2020, I started working in The Sydney Private Company as an Administration Officer and Account

Bookkeeper. I have acquired valuable experience in most of the administration and account booking

fields, such as client paperwork and financial settlements, completing other clerical tasks such as data

entry, management of customer invoicing and receipting of consultations, account bookings for

private and public clients, finalizing the customer list every day, and banking.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Accounting Assistant at TOP ELEVATORS PTY LTD - Sydney, NSW | May 2020 - current

Key responsibilities:

Reviewed and processed invoices, sales tax, and purchase orders, ensuring the accuracy

of all data

• Managed daily bookkeeping functions with attention to accounts receivable, accounts

payable, banking reconciliation, and disbursements

Maintained accuracy when reviewing and reconciling the general ledger

Maintained all accounting records and files, developed budget estimates, and worked

on professional financial forecasts

• Calculated taxes owed, prepared tax returns

• Followed detailed end-of-month accounting procedures to verify proper balancing of

all accounts and readiness for the new month

Handled payroll services for 30 employees successfully once a month

- Prepared weekly payroll for a team of salaried and hourly employees
- · Reconciled all bank accounts monthly

Finance Manager at Ministry of Science Organisation - Tehran | Jul 2010 - Jun 2019

Key responsibilities:

- Prepared customer paperwork
- Managed the collection of excesses/co payments
- Completed other clerical tasks, as required, such as data entry with "Webpass"
- Performed checks
- Managed client invoicing and receipting of consultations
- Account bookings for private and public clients
- Issuing accounts and collecting payments and processing
- Worked collaboratively and effectively to develop positive working relationships with a wide range of stakeholders
- Ordered tolls
- Excellent attention to detail and well-developed problem-solving and analytical skills
- Competency in the use of IT systems
- Banking at the end of each day

Accounting Clerk at Art Tehran University - Tehran | Apr 2007 - Jul 2010

Key responsibilities:

- Prepared monthly and year-end closing statements, financial documents, and invoices
- Communicated with senior accounting staff about discrepancies and devised plans to reconcile financial issues
- Resolved billing discrepancies by completing detailed research and analysis and documented client rebate discounts and reserve fund records
- Processed both outgoing and incoming payments and invoices
- Balanced reports and batch summaries to submit for approval

Hassan Jafari Page 2 | 4

- Managed daily bookkeeping functions with attention to accounts receivable, accounts payable, banking reconciliation, and disbursements
- Reconciled all bank accounts monthly
- Prepared weekly payroll for a team of salaried and hourly employees
- Completed daily computer backups, checked for viruses, and updated programs
- Helped the company move to a paperless system and save substantial printing costs

Accounting Bookkeeper at Asia Insurance Company - Tehran | Dec 2003 - Apr 2007

Key responsibilities:

- Processed invoices and checks and maintained daily cash logs and deposits
- Organized and maintained the chart of accounts and updated monthly entries and adjustments, including payroll entries
- Reviewed transactions, issued checks, and updated ledgers and budgets
- Managed accounting closings, accounts payable, and financial reporting for multiple clients
- Completed day-to-day financial transactions
- Tracked employee time and attendance for payroll
- Processed customer payments and set up payment plans
- Prepared and mailed client invoices within expected timeframes to promote likelihood of on-time payments
- Completed daily computer backups, checked for viruses and updated programs

EDUCATION

Financial accounting

Faran High Education Tehran

Bachelor 2009

computer-Hardware from

Azad University Tehran

Diploma 2002

CERTIFICATES

Hassan Jafari Page 3 | 4

• Diploma in Accounting of financial

Tehran informatic College. Tehran. Iran 2003

• Diploma in General Accounting

Tehran informatic College. Tehran. Iran 2000

SKILLS

- Experienced in XERO/TECHONE
- Highly experienced WEBPASS
- Highly experienced in HOLOO accounting software
- Experienced in HAMKARAN SYSTEM accounting software
- High level in Microsoft Office including Excel and Word
- Payroll processing
- Data entry
- General office Administration

PERSONAL DETAILS

- Ability to work under pressure, independently and as a team member
- Excellent customer facing, communication and rapport building skills
- Able to prioritize in a complex, fast-paced environment

LANGUAGES

- English (intermediate)
- Persian (Native)

REFERENCES

Available on request

Hassan Jafari Page 4 | 4